A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, Projects, SG 1.24 (A98) FA1295
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Rockefeller Foundation (RF), 1983-1998
  - RF 91003 A 120 - Malaysian Agricultural Research and Development Institute - Genetic Manipulation of Indica Rice, 1988-1997 (Box R3098)
  - RF 91010 A 3 - Sahel Institute - Health Transition Project, 1988-1994 (Box R3099)
  - RF 91012 - Harvard University-University of Sussex - Eliminating Chemical Biological Weapons, 1991-1995 (Box R3099)
  - RF 91013 A 491 - University of Maryland - Resident Fellows (Spanish and Portugese), 1987-1995 (Box R3099)
  - RF 91015 A 46 - University of California - Sacred Arts of Vodoun Exhibition, 1989-1996 (Box R3099)
  - RF 91015 A 48 - Hermandad de Artistas Graficos de Puerto Rico - Puerto Rican Film Text, 1990-1994 (Box R3099)
  - RF 91025 A 95 - Philadelphia Alliance for Teaching Humanities in the Schools - Student Writing and World History, 1984-1996 (Box R3100)
  - RF 91025 A 95 - Philadelphia Alliance for Teaching Humanities in the Schools - Student Writing and World History, 1984-1996 (Box R3101)
  - RF 91025 A 96 - Smithsonian Institution - Washington, D.C. Superintendent's Academy for the Humanities, 1988-1996 (Box R3102)
  - RF 91031 A 295 - Javeriana University - Klevens, 1991-1995 (Box R3102)
  - RF 91031 A 298 - University of North Carolina - Internal Evaluation of Inclen, 1989-1994 (Box R3102)
  - RF 91031 A 314 - University of Health Sciences - Sathianathan, 1991-1993 (Box R3102)
  - RF 91031 A 334 - University of Nairobi - Sickle Cell Anemia in Children, 1991-1995 (Box R3102)
  - RF 91036 A 1 - International Youth Foundation - Foundations-Like Organizations, 1991-1993 (Box R3102)
  - RF 91037 A 199 - Yelengi, Nikasa Tekilazaya, 1991-1993; 1997 (Box R3103)
  - RF 91037 A 201 - Gwanfogbe, Philomenia, 1991-1994; 1997 (Box R3103)
  - RF 91037 A 256 - Camera, Alpha - Adia: Childhood Toxocara Canis Infection in Guinea, 1991-1994 (Box R3103)
  - RF 91037 A 260 - Forjouh, Samuel - Adia: Burns in Children In Ghana, 1991-1997 (Box R3103)
  - RF 91048 A 8 - University of Maryland - Public Policy Analysis Post-Doctural Program, 1987-1995 (Box R3103)
  - RF 91055 A 132 - Zhang Shang-Hong (Rescinded), 1991; 1996 (Box R3103)
  - RF 91055 A 133 - Persechini, Pedro Muanis, 1991-1994; 1997-1998 (Box R3103)
  - RF 91055 A 135 - Krishna, Amitabh, 1991-1994; 1997 (Box R3103)
  - RF 91055 A 136 - Lohia, Anuradha, 1991-1995; 1998 (Box R3103)
  - RF 91055 A 137 - Mathur, Premendu Prakash, 1988-1996 (Box R3103)
  - RF 91055 A 140 - Ogunrinade, Adelani Folasayo, 1987-1994 (Box R3103)
  - RF 91055 A 142 - Karande, Anjali Anoop - Biotechnology Career Fellowship, 1991-1995 (Box R3103)
  - RF 91055 A 143 - Abdel-Aal, Yehia, A. I., 1987-1996 (Box R3104)
  - RF 91055 A 144 - Benaim, Gustavo - Biotechnology Career Fellowship, 1991-1995 (Box R3104)
  - RF 91055 A 146 - Ramamurthy, Viraraghavan - Biotechnology Career Fellowship, 1991-1996 (Box R3104)
  - RF 91055 A 147 - Vadillo-Ortega, Felipe - Matrix Metalloproteinases and Premature Membrane Rupture, 1991-1995 (Box R3104)
  - RF 91055 A 151 - Panneerselvam, Chinnakkaunnu, 1988-1995; 1998 (Box R3104)
  - RF 91055 A 152 - Ma Quing-Sheng (Rescinded), 1984-1993 (Box R3104)
  - RF 91055 A 153 - Ramaiah, K.V. Atchuta - Biotechnology Career Fellowship (Rescinded), 1989-1990; 1998 (Box R3104)
  - RF 91055 A 154 - Mahadevan, Subramony - Biotechnology Career Fellowship, 1991-1995 (Box R3104)
  - RF 91055 A 155 - Rao, A. Jagannadha, 1985-1996 (Box R3104)
  - RF 91055 A 156 - University of the Philippines at Los Banos - Biotechnology Career Fellowship for Narceo B. Bajet, 1991-1996 (Box R3104)
  - RF 91055 A 158 - Universidad Nacional Autonoma de Mexico - Biotechnology Career Fellowship for Dr. Maria del Carmen Clapp Jimenez L., 1987-1996 (Box R3105)
  - RF 91058 A 58 - Worby, Eric William, 1991-1997 (Box R3105)
  - RF 91058 A 62 - Marsh, Robin Ruth - Social Science Research Fellowship in Agriculture, 1991-1997 (Box R3105)
  - RF 91058 A 63 - Aw-Hassan, Aden Abdullah - Social Science Research Fellowship, 1991-1997 (Box R3105)
  - RF 91058 A 64 - Ndoye, Ousseynou - Social Science Research Fellowship: Commercialization Possibilities for Non-Traditional Crops in Forest Zone of Africa, 1992-1997 (Box R3105)
  - RF 91058 A 65 - Sunderlin, William Dana - Social Science Research Fellowship: Management Options and Strategies for Common Property Fishery Resources, 1991-1997 (Box R3105)
  - RF 91058 A 68 - Turner, Matthew - Social Science Research Fellowship: Effects of Economic and Ecological Changes on Livestock in Sudano-Sahelian Zone of West Africa, 1991-1997 (Box R3105)
  - RF 91064 - International Youth Foundation - Esquel Group Foundation, 1991-1994 (Box R3105)
  - RF 91068 A 100 - Billops, Camille - KKK Boutique Ain't Just Rednecks, 1991-1993 (Box R3105)
  - RF 91068 A 101 - Bordowitz, Gregg - Dense Moments Without Reason, 1992-1995 (Box R3106)
  - RF 91075 - New York University - Substance Abuse in the Inner City, 1990-1997; 2 files. (Box R3106)
  - RF 91076 - New York Community Trust - New York City Arts Institutions, 1991-1996 (Box R3106)
  - RF 91077 A 7 - Cold Spring Harbor Laboratory - Enable Scientists to Attend Plant Genetics and Breeding Course, 1994; 1997 (Box R3106)
  - RF 91079 A 30 - University of California (San Francisco) - Heterosexual Transmission of HIV, 1988-1993 (Box R3106)
  - RF 91079 A 31 - Columbia University - AIDS Projects in Senegal and Uganda, 1988-1995 (Box R3106)
  - RF 91079 A 35 - Population Council - AIDS Prevention Project in Thailand, 1991-1995 (Box R3107)
  - RF 91080 A 133 - Rockefeller University - Control of Chagas Disease in Argentina, 1991-1996 (Box R3107)
  - RF 91080 A 134 - New England Medical Center Hospitals, Inc. - Meeting of Diarrheal Disease Research Partners, 1992-1993 (Box R3107)
  - RF 91080 A 135 - University of California (Los Angeles) - Pathogenic Kinetoplastids, 1988-1995 (Box R3107)
  - RF 91080 A 136 - Pasteur Institute (France) - Human Vivax Malaria, 1988-1995 (Box R3107)
  - RF 91080 A 142 - University of California (San Francisco) - Drug Development and Resistance in Plasmodium, 1988-1995 (Box R3107)
  - RF 91080 A 145 - Harvard University - China-U.S. Partnership on Schistosomiasis and Filarsis, 1987-1993; 1996 (Box R3107)
  - RF 91080 A 152 - Brown University - Philippine Schistosomiasis, 1987-1995 (Box R3108)
  - RF 91080 A 156 - National Polytechnic Institute of Tropical Medicine (Mexico City) - National Institute of Nutritional Diseases - Protozoan International Diseases, 1988-1994 (Box R3108)
  - RF 91080 A 160 - Research Institute of Tropical Medicine - WHO-TDR-RF Partnership Schistosomiasis Symposium, 1991-1996 (Box R3108)
  - RF 91080 A 162 - Christian Medical College and Hospital - Diarrheal Disease, 1988-1997 (Box R3108)
  - RF 91080 A 163 - Center for Genetic Engineering and Biotechnology Investigations - Enteric Infections in Childhood, 1988-1995; 4 files. (Box R3109)
  - RF 91083 A 94 - Kennedy, Eileen - Women's Status in Marital Fertility, Nutrition and Health, Kenya, 1990-1995 (Box R3109)
  - RF 91083 A 98 - Addis Ababa University - Women's Fertility in Ethiopia, 1991-1995 (Box R3109)
  - RF 91083 A 104 - Institute of Agricultural Research - Allocation of Women's Time and Effect on Fertility-Nutrition, 1991-1997 (Box R3109)
  - RF 91083 A 108 - Tumwesigye, Mary B. - Demographics Studies, 1991-1992; 1996 (Box R3110)
  - RF 91083 A 113 - African Medical and Research Foundation - Lukhando, 1990-1996 (Box R3110)
  - RF 91083 A 114 - Mahidol University - Enable African Scholars to Pursue Masters Degrees, 1990-1995 (Box R3110)
  - RF 91084 A 279 - Rahman, Mizanur - Impact of Grameen Bank on Women's Status and Fertility: Bangladesh, 1991-1995 (Box R3110)
  - RF 91087 A 10 - Ota, Cleaver - Re-Entry Awards: Monitor Educational Progress in Zimbabwe, 1991-1992 (Box R3110)
  - RF 91087 A 12 - Hyde, Karin - Girls Achievement in Malawi Secondary Schools, 1992-1993; 1996 (Box R3110)
  - RF 91087 A 15 - Ngau, Margaret M. - Re-Entry Award: Female Education in Kenya, 1992-1994 (Box R3110)
  - 1991-0102-0007 - Public Broadcasting Service Retreat - Integrating Technology and Development for Education, 1994 (Box R3110)
  - RF 91104 - Hispanic Federation of New York - Services to Member Agencies, 1991-1994 (Box R3110)
  - RF 92001 A 150 - University of Tokyo - Isolation, Characterization and Mapping of CDNA Clones in Rice, 1991-1995 (Box R3110)
  - RF 92001 A 158 - Universite de Fribourg (Switzerland) - Molecular Signaling During Systemic Acquired Resistance in Rice, 1992-1998 (Box R3110)
  - RF 92001 A 163 - Swiss Federal Institute of Technology (Eth Zurich) - Genetic Transformation System, 1990-1997 (Box R3110)
  - RF 92001 A 172 - University of Missouri - Cytokinins and Control of Rice Endosperm Development, 1989-1994 (Box R3110)
  - RF 92002 A 13 - International Rice Research Institute (IRRI) - Research on Molecular Markers by Dr. Hittalmani, 1991-1995 (Box R3111)
  - RF 92003 A 148 - Osania University (India) - Anther Culture in Indica Rice, 1989-1996 (Box R3111)
  - RF 92003 A 159 - Chinese Academy of Sciences - Agrobacterium Tumefaciens Mediated Transformation of Rice, 1992-1996 (Box R3111)
  - RF 92003 A 162 - Fujian Agricultural College (China) - Rice Tungro Bacilliform Virus Coat Protein Gene Transformed Rice Plants, 1992-1997 (Box R3111)
  - RF 92004 A 5 - Rutgers University - Choice of Research Technique and Crop: A Case Study of Plant Biotechnology in India, 1991-1994 (Box R3111)
  - RF 92004 A 8 - International Service for the Acquisition of Agri-Biotech Applications (ISAAA) - Crops Workshop, 1993-1996 (Box R3111)
  - RF 92006 A 18 - Makerere University (Uganda) - Establish Uganda Soil Erosion Network, 1992-1993; 1996 (Box R3111)
  - RF 92006 A 21 - Makerere University - Soil Erosion Study, 1991-1993; 1996 (Box R3111)
  - RF 92006 A 23 - International Institute of Biological Control (Kenya) - Assessing Water Hyacinth Infestations, 1993-1996 (Box R3111)
  - RF 92014 A 56 - Universidad Nacional Autonoma de Mexico - Ovarian Differentiation in Mammals, 1992-1996 (Box R3111)
  - RF 92014 A 59 - Shanghai Academy of Social Sciences - Old-Age Security Pension Systems Effect on Fertility Rates, 1992-1996 (Box R3111)
  - RF 92014 A 63 - University of Ibadan - Sexuality of Nigerian Adolescents, 1992-1994 (Box R3111)
  - RF 92014 A 66 - Campomar Foundation - Institute of Biochemical Investigations (Argentina) - Modulation of Calcium Homeostasis in Sertoli Cells, 1993-1994 (Box R3111)
  - RF 92017 A 503 - University of New Mexico - Resident Fellows (Southwest Hispanics), 1988-1995 (Box R3111)
  - RF 92018 A 1 - International African Institute, London - West African Museums Project (WAMP), 1988-1994; 2 files. (Box R3112)
  - RF 92018 A 5 - Southern Africa Development Coordination Conference Association of Museums (Namibia) - Training Museum Educators, 1992-1996 (Box R3112)
  - RF 92019 A 59 - University of California (Los Angeles) - Wight Art Gallery Exhibition, 1991-1994 (Box R3112)
  - RF 92019 A 64 - Arizona State University - Too Late for Goya Exhibition, 1991-1994 (Box R3112)
  - RF 92019 A 67 - American Center for Student and Artists, Inc. - Landscape as Metaphor (Cancelled), 1992-1996 (Box R3112)
  - RF 92026 - New School for Social Research - Social Effects of Community Development, 1990-1995 (Box R3112)
  - RF 92034 A 371 - Escola Paulista de Medicina (Brazil) - A Qualitative Assessment on Family Life With Schizophrenic Member, 1992-1993 (Box R3112)
  - RF 92034 A 376 - University of Chile - Neurotoxic Effects of Methyl Bromide, 1992-1993 (Box R3112)
  - RF 92034 A 377 - West China University of Medical Sciences - Transmission of Hepatitis B in Chengdu, 1992-1995 (Box R3113)
  - RF 92034 A 378 - Shanghai Medical University - An Epidemiology Study of Mushroom Workers' Lung, 1992-1993 (Box R3113)
  - RF 92034 A 379 - Addis Ababa University - Head Injuries with Risk Factors and Prevention, 1992-1993 (Box R3113)
  - RF 92034 A 14 - Foundation for Environmental Development and Education in Nigeria (Feden) - General Support for the Start-Up Phase, 1992-1994 (Box R3113)
  - RF 92038 A 263 - Ndegwa, Stephen - Adia: Political Impact of NGO's in Kenya, 1991-1997 (Box R3113)
  - RF 92038 A 283 - Johns, Jomo - Adia: Rice Straw Brewers Grains Diet for Ruminants, 1991-1997 (Box R3113)
  - RF 92038 A 289 - Hakiza, Johnson J. - Adia: Corn Leaf Blight, 1992-1995 (Box R3113)
  - RF 92038 A 293 - Samuel, Mesfin - Adia: Stress, Coping and Resilence in Ethiopian Children, 1992-1997 (Box R3113)
  - RF 92038 A 301 - Natsa, Albert - Adia: Literacy in Zimbabwe, 1992-1995 (Box R3113)
  - RF 92038 A 307 - Ndjeunga, Jupiter - Adia: Financial Dualism in West Africa, 1992-1995 (Box R3113)
  - RF 92038 A 311 - Jumare, Ibrahim - Adia: Land Tenure in Nigeria, 1992-1997 (Box R3113)
  - RF 92038 A 317 - Kedera, Chagema John - Adia: Corn Disease Research, 1992-1997 (Box R3113)
  - RF 92038 A 321 - Rweyemanu, Cornel - Adia: Assessment of Phosphate Rock in Tanzania, 1991-1998 (Box R3114)
  - RF 92038 A 330 - Okeyo, Ruphina - Adia: Fuelwood Availability, Women's Time, Household Fuel Consumption, 1992-1995 (Box R3114)
  - RF 92038 A 339 - Kipligat, Peter Kenneth - Adia: Dynamics of Regional Integration in New World Order, 1992-1994; 1997 (Box R3114)
  - RF 92038 A 341 - Michigan State University - Adia Recognition Grant, 1993; 1998 (Box R3114)
  - RF 92038 A 342 - Gebreselassie, Hailmichael - Adia: Effect of Iron Supplementation on Ethiopian Children with Malaria, 1992-1997 (Box R3114)
  - RF 92038 A 344 - Elia, Frank M.E. - Adia: Genetic Controls in Common Bean, 1992-1997 (Box R3114)
  - RF 93038-431 - Iowa State University - African Dissertation Internship Awards Recognition Grant, 1994; 1998 (Box R3114)
  - RF 93038-432 - University of Pennsylvania - African Dissertation Internship Awards Recognition Grant, 1994; 1998 (Box R3114)
  - RF 92040 A 84 - Alternate Roots, Inc. - Interdisciplinary Artists, 1991-1995 (Box R3114)
  - RF 92040 A 98 - Lower Manhattan Cultural Council, Inc. - Implement Regional Initiative in New York State, 1992-1994 (Box R3114)
  - RF 92071 A 18 - University of Ghana - 20th American Literature Association Conference, 1993-1994; 1997 (Box R3115)
  - RF 92072 A 111 - Berlinger, Alan - The Mountain of Names, 1993-1996 (Box R3115)
  - RF 92072 A 112 - Minh-ha, Trinh T. - A Tale of Love, 1993; 1996 (Box R3115)
  - RF 92072 A 113 - Araki, Gregg - The Separation of Earth from its Axis, 1992-1993; 1996 (Box R3115)
  - RF 92072 A 114 - Andrews, Lawrence - Fantasy Island, 1993; 1996 (Box R3115)
  - RF 92072 A 115 - Benning, James - Crossing Utah, 1992-1995 (Box R3115)
  - RF 92072 A 116 - Aparicio, Carlos - Open Wounds, 1993-1996 (Box R3115)
  - RF 92072 A 117 - High, Kathy - Substitute Families, 1993-1996 (Box R3115)
  - RF 92072 A 118 - Bowman, Arlene - Crossing Over, 1992-1995 (Box R3115)
  - RF 92072 A 119 - Suleiman, Elia, 1993; 1996 (Box R3115)
  - RF 92072 A 120 - Wallner, Martha - Sarah Laughed, 1992-1993; 1996 (Box R3115)
  - RF 92072 A 121 - Benning, Sadie - Girl Power, 1993; 1996 (Box R3115)
  - RF 92072 A 122 - Troyano, Ela - The Cooking Show, 1993; 1996 (Box R3115)
  - RF 92072 A 123 - Katz, Leandro - El Dia Que Me Quieras, 1992-1993; 1996 (Box R3115)
  - RF 92072 A 124 - Poole, Thomas - Not Channel Zero's Grassroots Video Cookbook, 1993; 1996 (Box R3115)
  - RF 92072 A 127 - National Asian American Television Communications Association - 1993-94 Living Room Festival, 1993-1994 (Box R3115)
  - RF 92072 A 128 - Video Repetoire, LTD - South Central Los Angeles: Inside Voices, A Documentary, 1993-1997 (Box R3115)
  - RF 92072 A 130 - Deep Dish T. V., Inc. - Film Documentary: Beyond L. A., 1993-1995 (Box R3115)
  - RF 92072 A 131 - Echo Productions: Film Documentary: The Kontum Diary, 1993-1995 (Box R3115)
  - RF 92072 A 137 - Hofman, Fabian - Los Ferro, 1994-1996 (Box R3115)
  - RF 92072 A 138 - Pensotti, Mariano Alejo - Dreaming About Wolves and Giraffes, 1994-1996 (Box R3116)
  - RF 92072 A 139 - Omar de Noronha Squeff, Arthur - "Magnetic Choices" Video, 1994-1996 (Box R3116)
  - RF 92072 A 141 - Calderon, Alberto Cortes - Violeta, 1994-1996 (Box R3116)
  - RF 92072 A 142 - Cuevas, Ximena - Rounds in the City, 1994-1996 (Box R3116)
  - RF 92078 - Urban Strategies Council - Secretariat for Community Planning and Action, 1991-1995 (Box R3116)
  - RF 92079 - New York Public Library - Science, Industry and Business Library, 1992-1995 (Box R3116)
  - RF 92087 A 17 -, 1990-1996 (Box R3116)
  - RF 92089 - Macro International, Inc. - Safe Motherhood Initiative, 1992-1995 (Box R3116)
  - RF 92091 - International Women's Health Coalition - Reproductive Health in Sub-Saharan Africa, 1987-1995; 4 files. (Box R3117)
  - RF 92092 A 49 - Institute of Tropical Medicine (Belgium) - STD's and HIV in Female Prostitutes in Abidjan, 1992-1994 (Box R3117)
  - RF 92092 A 53 - Center for Study and Research in Collective Health (Brazil) - Sexual Behavior Research, 1992-1995 (Box R3118)
  - RF 92092 A 60 - International Family Health - HIV-AIDS NGO Support Programme, 1992-1994 (Box R3118)
  - RF 92092 A 62 - Commonwealth Youth Programme Africa Centre (Zambia) - Publication of Conference Proceedings for Young People with HIV-AIDS, 1992-1994 (Box R3118)
  - RF 92092 A 65 - Fund for the City of New York - Children and Adolescents Orphaned by AIDS, 1993-1994 (Box R3118)
  - RF 92093 A 5 - Council for Renewable Energy Education (CREE) - Renewable Energy Projects in World Bank Loans to Brazil, 1993-1996 (Box R3118)
  - RF 92093 A 8 - Enersol Associates, Inc. - Solar-Based Electrification in the Dominican Republic and Honduras, 1992-1997 (Box R3118)
  - RF 92093 A 10 - University of Tennessee - Biomass-To-Electricity in Yunnan Province and Integrated Energy Resource Planning in Hainan Province, 1992-1995 (Box R3118)
  - RF 92094 A 24 - Sebakwane, Shirley M. - Educational Management in South Africa, 1992-1994 (Box R3118)
  - RF 92094 A 40 - Wprld Bank - Seminars on Girls' Education in Sahel, 1993-1996 (Box R3118)
  - RF 92095 A 30 - Foundation for Education (FEDU) (Namibia) - Mathematics Kits, 1993-1997 (Box R3118)
  - RF 92099 A 100 - Dance Theater Foundation Inc. - Collaborative Theater-Dance Work, 1992-1996 (Box R3119)
  - RF 92099 A 102 -Foundation for Independent Artists, Inc. - Reality, 1992-1996 (Box R3119)
  - RF 92099 A 108 - Miami Light Project, Inc. - Original Work by Culture Clash, 1992-1996 (Box R3119)
  - RF 92099 A 110 - June Watanabe Dance Co. - A Room of Our Own, 1992-1995 (Box R3119)
  - RF 92099 A 114 - Seven Stages, Inc. - New Plays, 1992-1994 (Box R3119)
  - RF 92099 A 122 - Carpetbag Theater, Inc. - Production Based on Historical African-American Economic Development, 1992-1996 (Box R3119)
  - RF 92099 A 125 - Ping Chong and Company - Deshima, 1990-1994 (Box R3119)
  - RF 92099 A 126 - Pauline Oliveros Foundation, Inc. - "Nzinga", Musical Theater Work, 1989-1996 (Box R3119)
  - RF 92099 A 127 - St. Ann Center for Restoration of the Arts - The Comedian Harmonists, 1991-1995 (Box R3119)
  - RF 92100 A 47 - Los Angeles Festival - 1993 Festival, 1990-1996 (Box R3119)
  - RF 92100 A 52 - Junebug Productions, Inc. - Environmental Festival Planning Conference, 1993; 1996 (Box R3119)
  - RF 92100 A 57 - Jacob's Pillow Dance Festival, Inc. - 1993 International Artist Residencies Program (Box R3119)
  - RF 92100 A 58 - Contemporary Arts Center - 1994 Live Arts Festival: Reworking the Roots: A Neo-Hoodoo Happening, 1993-1994 (Box R3119)
  - RF 92103 - Carter Center - Atlanta Project Community Action and Fund-Raising Strategies, 1992-1997; 2 files. (Box R3120)
  - RF 92108 - Coalition of Community Foundations for Youth, 1989-1995; 4 files total. (Box R3120)
  - RF 92108 - Coalition of Community Foundations for Youth, 1989-1995; 4 files total. (Box R3121)
  - RF 92108 A 4 - Arizona Community Foundation - Partnership for Children, 1991-1994 (Box R3121)
  - RF 92117 - Urban Institute - Human Service Delivery System in San Antonio, 1990-1994 (Box R3121)
  - RF 92118 - Wilson, Woodrow (National Fellowship) Foundation - Public Policy Training Program, 1989-1997; 3 files (Box R3122)
  - RF 92121 A 37 - Foundation for the National Capital Region - Comerization in the District of Columbia Public Schools, 1993-1994 (Box R3122)
  - RF 92121 A 41 - KQED, Inc. - Maggie's American Dream: The Life and Times of a Black Family, 1993-1994 (Box R3122)
  - 1992-0121-0044 - Association of Supervision and Curriculum Development - Second Comer Satellite Broadcast, 1994-1996 (Box R3122)
  - RF 93001 A 179 - University of Missouri (Columbia) - Rice Breeding, 1987-1997 (Box R3122)
  - RF 93001 A 182 - Rice Transformation Summit, 1993-1996 (Box R3123)
  - RF 93001 A 187 - University of California (Davis) - Yeast Artificial Chromosome (YAC) Libraries for Rice, 1993-1995 (Box R3123)
  - RF 93001 A 188 - Texas A&M University - Yeast Artificial Chromosome (YAC) Libraries for Rice, 1993; 1997-1998 (Box R3123)
  - RF 93001 A 195 - Michigan State University - Genetic Characterization in Brown Planthopper, 1990-1994 (Box R3123)
  - RF 93003 A 180 - Purdue University - Genetic Transformation of Indica Rice, 1992-1997 (Box R3123)
  - RF 93003 A 181 - University of Wisconsin - Molecular Basis of Genome Instability in Magnaporthe Grisea, 1992-1994 (Box R3123)
  - RF 93003 A 189 - National Center for Genetic Engineering and Biotechnology (Thailand) - Workshop on Rice Transformation, 1993-1996 (Box R3123)
  - RF 93003 A 192 - United States - Agriculture (Dept. of) - Plant Genome II Meeting, 1992-1994 (Box R3123)
  - RF 93009 A 2 - Population Resource Center - Publishing Executive Summaries for 1994 Cairo Conference, 1993-1994 (Box R3123)
  - RF 93009 A 5 - Population Council - Family, Gender and Population Policy Debates, 1993-1995 (Box R3123)
  - RF 93009 A 7 -Moffett, George D. - III - Produce Book for Delegates to the 1994 Cairo Conference, 1993-1996 (Box R3123)
  - RF 93009 A 9 - Deutsche Stiftung Veltbevokerung - Pre 1994 United Nations-Cairo Conference Meeting, 1993-1995 (Box R3123)
  - RF 93009 A 10 - International Center for the Scientific Study of Population (Belgium) - Pre United Nations-Cairo Conference Meeting, 1993-1994 (Box R3123)
  - 939912-2 - Rockefeller Foundation - Program Operations - Conference on Media Pluralism in West Africa, 1994; 1997 (Box R3124)
  - RF 93013 A 519 - Research Foundation of the City University of New York - Retreat and Colloquia for RF Fellows Programs, 1993-1994; 1998 (Box R3124)
  - RF 93013 A 520 - American Film Foundation - Tales from the Center of the Universe, 1993; 1998 (Box R3124)
  - RF 93013 A 522 - Center for Educational Telecommunications - Retreat-Workshop on Asian-American History, 1993-1995 (Box R3124)
  - RF 93013 A 524 - City University of New York - The Role of CUNY Educators, 1993-1995; 1998 (Box R3124)
  - RF 93014 A 74 - Robert Abbe Museum of Stone Age Antiquities - Art of Tomah Joseph, 1993-1994 (Box R3124)
  - RF 93014 A 75 - Cleveland Center for Contemporary Art - Outside the Frame, 1993; 1996 (Box R3124)
  - RF 93014 A 76 - Museum of Modern Art - Exhibition - Latin American Artists of the 20th Century, 1992-1996 (Box R3124)
  - RF 93014 A 77 - Alternative Center for International Arts, Inc. - Rupert Garcia Exhibition, 1992-1994 (Box R3124)
  - RF 93014 A 78 - Mexican Museum - "Ceremony of Memory II" Exhibition, 1992-1995 (Box R3124)
  - RF 93014 A 79 - Edmundson Art Foundation - American Indian Parfleche Exhibition, 1993-1996 (Box R3124)
  - RF 93014 A 80 - Rutgers University - "Recovering Histories" in Chile Exhibition, 1992-1994 (Box R3124)
  - RF 93014 A 82 - Houston Fotofest - "American Voices" Exhibition, 1992-1995 (Box R3124)
  - RF 93014 A 85 - Denver Art Museum - Landscape as Metaphor, 1992-1995 (Box R3125)
  - RF 93014 A 87 - Amigos Del Museo Del Barrio, Inc. - Bilingual Catalogue: 1994 Exhibition "Recovering History" Exhibition, 1992-1993; 1996 (Box R3125)